egully.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy

**(dated 01/10/2009)**

We appreciate the trust you have placed with  by choosing our service. That's why we insist upon the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy. Each time you use the website, you should check the date of this Privacy Notice (which appears above) and review any changes that have been made since your last visit to the Site. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Notice, please do not use the Site. 

This Privacy Notice is posted to demonstrate our leadership in online security and customer service practices. We treat your information with the same honesty and sensitivity that we have displayed throughout our company's history. 

**1\. Personal Information collected by Egully.com**  

Egully.com.com uses information that we collect from our visitors and customers to personalize and improve your visit and shopping experience at the webite. We gather the following types of information: 

**Information You Give to Us:** We Collect Personal Information that is provided by customers. “Personal Information” includes your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, date of birth, IP address. Personal Information is collected when you establish an account with us, place an order on the website, sweepstakes or on-line survey, or when you communicate with any of our departments such as customer service, sales or technical services through the website, telephone, mail or fax. 

**Cookies:   **Through the use of cookies, we may also collect and analyze the IP address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as your browser type and version; operating system and platform; purchase history; confirmation when you open e-mail that we send you; and the URLs which lead you to and around the website including the date and time. You can generally set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie. Software is also available from third parties which will allow you to visit the Site without providing this information. You are welcome to use the website if you use such software but we will not be able to offer you our personalized services and we will be unable to accept any online orders from you.

**Web Beacons:   **We (or service providers on our behalf) may collect information from visits to the webshrough the use of “Web Beacons.” Web Beacons are web page elements which may employ cookie technology that enable us to record data about visits to or transactions made on the website. This information is sometimes known as “clickstream data.” We may use this data to analyze trends and statistics to improve your online experience or our customer service. No Personal Information is collected through the use of Web Beacons on the Site. 

**2\. Use of Information Gathered**

 We and the third parties who provide services related to will use the information referenced above to fulfill your order and provide services related to or the operation of our business. Examples of these services include payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, order fulfillment and shipping, Web site evaluation, data analysis and, where applicable, data cleansing. The third parties who provide any of these services are authorized to use this information only in connection with the services they are engaged to perform.

In addition to using the information to fulfill your purchase order, we also retain some of that information in our customer database. We use that information to track your order, to respond to your inquiries and to make subsequent purchases you wish to make easier and faster. We also may use that information, from time to time, to contact you concerning our products, services, sales or special promotions of egully.com. We try to limit those contacts to ones that might be of interest to you. 

Our website links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Egully.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites. 

**3\. Security**  

We employ High-Grade AES 256-bit encryption technology in all areas of the website which require you to provide your personal or account information, including those areas related to online ordering, order status, catalog request and contest forms. The website utilizes industry-standard firewalls and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to allow for the encryption of potentially sensitive Personal Information, such as your name, address and telephone number. 

You should recognize, however, that no computer system is fully secure and that there are inherent risks associated with Internet transactions. To make sure you have the latest security features on your browser, you may want to download the most recent version of your favorite browser, which should have full SSL support

3\. Information we collect

When you use our Site, we collect and store your personal information from you. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our Site to make your experience safer and easier. Importantly, we only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose. 

In general, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. To fully use our Site, you will need to register using our online registration form or transact as Guest User, where you may be required to provide us with your name, date of birth, contact number, email id, user id, password, residence / place of business information, billing information, shipping information. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Site. 

We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behavior on our site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. 

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Site and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session. 

If you choose to post messages on our message boards or other message areas or leave feedback for other users, we will collect that information you provide to us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. 

If you register for the Site on another web site or use a web site providing a service for egully or a web site that helps facilitates your activity on the Site, that web site may provide personal information about you and your transactions back to us. 

**4\. Our use of your information**

We use your personal information to facilitate the services you request. We use your personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site to: resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote safe trading; collect fees owed; measure consumer interest in the services provided by us, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our User Agreement; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your personal information to identify users using multiple User IDs/ eMail ID/ Contact Number or aliases. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy. 

You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve the Site's content and product offerings, and customize the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site. 

You agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you are a registered user and do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications in your profile. You may make changes to your profile at any time. 

**5\. REVIEWS AND COMMENTS**

Any reviews or comments submitted or posted on the website by the user including reviews, comments, ideas, know-how, questions, suggestions, techniques or information in any other form will be considered to be strictly non-confidential and non-proprietary. All the reviews and comments will be considered as the exclusive property of Egully.com. 

Egully.com shall have the worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty free and transferable rights to use, copy, modify, display, publish, distribute, sell, lease, adapt, transmit or use the information in any manner as deemed suitable by Egully.com.

Users submitting reviews and comments on the website grant Egully.com the right to use the name submitted with the review, comment or any other information provided. The user will be deemed to own the rights to the reviews and comments and use of the any such information by Egully.com will not infringe or violate the rights to any third party. Users shall not use false e-mail ids or misrepresent self while submitting reviews and comments.

**6\. Corrections/Information Removal/Opt-Out**  

If your name, e-mail or postal address, telephone number or other Personal Information changes, you may update, correct or omit the relevant information by contacting us at privacy@egully.com. In addition, if you no longer wish to receive communications from us you may opt-out by emailing us at privacy@egully.com, sending a letter to: Egully.com Privacy Officer, **803A, Devika Tower, 6, Nehru Place, Delhi 110019** or by clicking on the unsubscribe link within any marketing e-mail you receive from us.
